<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Delhi!</string>
    <string name="desc">Your one stop destination for all your Delhi travelling needs! We have all the spots, buzz and fun in store.</string>
    <string name="comedy">LOL Till You Fall At Vir Das Biggest Ever Comedy Show</string>
    <string name="formal">Five Formal Styles For Five Different Work Days</string>
    <string name="edc">Line Up tickets are out!</string>
    <string name="restaurant">The restaurant week is on!</string>
    <string name="topdishes">Top 10 Dishes to try!</string>
    <string name="coffee">A delicious cup at</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    //this is for the sub activities
    <string name="food_title_1">Top ten famous dishes of Delhi</string>
    <string name="food_stitle_1">Check out the places you can try out the best.</string>

    //this for sub sub activities
    <string name="title1">Paranthas</string>
    <string name="desc1">
        From being the perfect start to a “healthy” morning in most Delhi households,
        to a meal for hungry college students and even a late-night snack, paranthas are definitely
        on the top of the list when it comes to my favorite food in Delhi. Choose from a plain one or
        select a stuffing of your choice - potatoes, cauliflower, radish, eggs, keema, bananas or even last nights left
        over dal - the options are galore.
    </string>
    <string name="title2">Chaat</string>
    <string name="desc2">
        If there is one thing that keeps the Delhi food scene ticking it’s the Street Food.
        With a variety that is unmatched, eating on the streets of Delhi is a crash course in the history and culture
        of the place. Chandni Chowk is undoubtedly the Street Food Capital of Delhi, and while no guide book
        can actually pinpoint the best places for Chaat, there are some landmark food haunts that really stand out.
        Of course, if you aren’t willing to travel that far,fret not for there are plenty of options for street food in Delhi.
    </string>
    <string name="title3"></string>
    <string name="desc3"></string>
    <string name="title4"></string>
    <string name="desc4"></string>
    <string name="title5"></string>
    <string name="desc5"></string>
    <string name="title6"></string>
    <string name="desc6"></string>
    <string name="title7"></string>
    <string name="desc7"></string>
    <string name="title8"></string>
    <string name="desc8"></string>
    <string name="title9"></string>
    <string name="desc9"></string>
    <string name="title10"></string>
    <string name="desc10"></string>
</resources>
